<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security on Monpearte IT Solutions - IT Solutions for the Central and Far West of NSW</title>
    <link>https://monpearte.com.au/tags/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security on Monpearte IT Solutions - IT Solutions for the Central and Far West of NSW</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://monpearte.com.au/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Trends of 2019 - Information Security is a Business Problem</title>
      <link>https://monpearte.com.au/post/top-5-trends-of-2019-information-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://monpearte.com.au/post/top-5-trends-of-2019-information-security/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At the end of last year I had the privilege of working with a company around their information security.  They successfully achieved their ISO 27001 certification.  For a relatively small business that was an enormous effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the key reasons they were able to get certified is they realised that Information Security was a problem the entire business needed to attack.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Trends of 2019 - Say Goodbye to Passwords</title>
      <link>https://monpearte.com.au/post/top-5-trends-of-2019-no-more-passwords/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://monpearte.com.au/post/top-5-trends-of-2019-no-more-passwords/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;2019 is the year that we move on from passwords.&lt;img src=&#34;https://monpearte.com.au/images/bender-goodbye.jpg&#34; title=&#34;Goodbye Losers....I mean passwords!&#34; alt=&#34;Goodbye Losers....I mean passwords!&#34; align=right hspace=20&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone hates passwords.  IT people spend hours trying to enforce great habits, but somehow passwords always end up on sticky notes posted on a monitor.  Occasionally the sticky note is put in a drawer.  Nobody ever looks there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever the good intentions of everyone involved, passwords are just not working.  The great news is, things are changing and passwords are going to be a thing of the past.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Password Security is Important</title>
      <link>https://monpearte.com.au/post/why-password-security-is-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://monpearte.com.au/post/why-password-security-is-important/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While passwords can seem restrictive and difficult, ensuring you have secure passwords is important.  You may not think you have any information you want to protect, but look closer look.  Do you share passwords between systems? Is your banking login the same as Facebook and your email?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Does this sound like you?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>